Open the project file .
In the 3D tool bar, select the 3D pull tool.
The position of the virtual line can be added to the pull chain.
The mouse is suspended in the pull chain position.
The blue dot shows that a pull chain can be added here.
Click .
The pull chain on this side is added and completed.
It can also be operated in the same way in the 2D window.
Click .
Add the pull chain.
Between the two sides of the pull chain, the black box line is displayed.
When modeling, the pull chain will be boxed according to the black box line.
Switch to .
The left arrow can drag the pull head to the appropriate position.
Before modeling, in order to prevent the inner layer of the panel from penetrating,
it is possible to change the position of the pull chain.
Set its layer to .
.
After the simulation is stable, turn off the simulation.
Restore its layer to .
Add the pull chain and complete.
Zoom in to see the pull chain.
Find the pull head facing inwards.
Switch to the texture surface.
You can see that half of the pull chain is gray.
It means that this side of the pull chain is in the opposite direction.
Select this side with the move tool.
Click .
Select .
The pull chain is in the correct direction.
Again, stabilize and close the simulation.
After adding the pull chain, you can also drag the pull head with the left arrow.
Adjust the closed position of the pull chain again and simulate.
Updating the 3D effect.
Click .
You can delete the entire pull chain.
Next, I will briefly introduce the meaning of other options.
When the pull chain is added, the two sides are reversed.
You can click it to switch to the same direction.
The pull chain can also be re-activated and frozen.
Control the display and hiding of the component.
Click on the pull head to see the pull chain.
Click to delete.
It will delete the entire pull chain.
The surface rotation is the same as this function of the panel.
The rotation can be applied to an asymmetrical pull head.
In the case of an asymmetrical pull head,
Turn it over to change the left and right states.
Move a pull head with a certain distance.
You can reset the pull head position and restore the original position.
The other options are the same as the pull chain.
The added pull chain is the default style.
Next, you need to modify the pull chain style and specifications according to your needs.
Select the pull chain in the object window.
In the property editor, the information can display the name of the pull chain.
And rename it.
Enter the product number, supplier and other information below.
The function can set the pull chain as a single or double.
After selecting the double, you can select the pull head direction in the direction.
It is double or double.
The type of pull chain is set as a single.
Click on the triangle on the right of the type.
The type of pull chain can be set as a vertical pull chain.
Metal pull chain, nylon pull chain or invisible pull chain.
Here, select the metal pull chain.
The type of pull chain can be set as a pull ruler, pull head and pull piece.
The type of the index can be set as an open or closed tail.
And set the type of upper and lower part.
The specifications can be selected.
You can also customize it.
Set the width, weight and thickness of the pull chain.
Next, start editing the material pattern of the pull chain.
In the 3D window, select the moving tool.
Select the length or length of the pull.
In the property editor, you can check and edit the length of the pull chain.
Open the pull chain.
After closing, simulate the pull chain to open.
Ctrl plus Z to restore the original state.
The pull chain can be maintained in the open state.
The following two options can be selected in the direction of the pull chain.
And select the pull chain to open.
Which side of the pull chain is the pull head?
The particle diameter can adjust the particle distance of the pull chain.
Folding is used to adjust the folding strength and angle between the pull chain and the plate.
Below, the material is divided into the pull ruler and the pull band.
They can be edited separately.
The type of the pull ruler, select metal.
Below, select the metal preset as gold.
The color is similar to the color of the fabric.
Switch to the fabric.
Set its color to be the same as the fabric.
Single pull head or pull piece.
Pull head, pull piece and finger will be selected together.
In the property editor, you can modify its material properties.
Adjust to gold metal that is the same as the pull chain.
If you want to adjust each component separately, you need to use the option to select the moving tool.
Click on one of the components again.
Just select the component.
By doing this, you can edit the size and material properties of the single or overall pull head component.
After the pull chain is completed, select the pull chain in the object window.
Go to the property editor, right upper corner, click Save.
Save it as ZPS format.
Drag it to the object window when applied.
Or select the default pull chain in the object window.
Open in the single property editor.
Select this pull chain and open it.
The same as ZPS format.
Have the same as ZPS format.
Select ZPS format.
If you go to the property editor, you will see the same as ZPS format.
On the left side of the screen, there is a bar.